{
    "subject": "resource/Cory_Doctorow",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/Little_Brother_(Doctorow_novel)",
    "human_readable": "Cory Doctorow's notable work is 'Little Brother'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9067683219909668,
            "question": "Are there other works by Cory Doctorow besides 'Little Brother'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8081680536270142,
            "question": "Name a notable work by Cory Doctorow."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5655063986778259,
            "question": "What is Cory Doctorow known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3511200547218323,
            "question": "Who is the author of 'Little Brother'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31498175859451294,
            "question": "Which book is titled 'Little Brother'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2721356451511383,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in 'Little Brother'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2596864402294159,
            "question": "Has 'Little Brother' been adapted into other media?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2302584946155548,
            "question": "What impact has 'Little Brother' had on readers and/or society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19642412662506104,
            "question": "What genre might the book 'Little Brother' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17316961288452148,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Cory Doctorow's writing style?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Cory Doctorow's notable work is 'Little Brother'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8009_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might the book 'Little Brother' belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8009_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact has 'Little Brother' had on readers and/or society?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8009_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has 'Little Brother' been adapted into other media?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8009_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8009_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8009_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8009_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8009_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8009_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8009_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8009_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8009_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8009_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8009_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}